<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>security on duck's pond</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/tags/security/</link><description>Recent content in security on duck's pond</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://qua3k.github.io/tags/security/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hacking Whonix onto Hyper-V</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/guides/whonix/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/guides/whonix/</guid><description>Hi, disclaimer, this is not officially supported by Whonix so expect no support.
Whonix does not have UEFI support at the moment, so you will have to resort to this guide hacking UEFI together if you want to run Generation 2 virtual machines.
Download Whonix and Virtualbox
qemu-imgis broken when trying to convert to vhdx. Verify the authenticity of the downloaded files. Extract the image with your archive utility of choice</description></item><item><title>Email (In)security</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/security/email/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/security/email/</guid><description>There is no such thing as secure email. Email is an inherently insecure protocol, conceived at a time when security was an afterthought. There are fundamental flaws with email that cannot be mitigated by slapping encryption on top.
Problems with… Email Authentication Sender Policy Framework is a protocol used to authorize the mail transfer agents allowed to send mail on behalf of a domain. However, SPF alone is almost useless in protecting against spoofing as it is designed to protect against forged senders and not forged headers shown in clients.</description></item><item><title>ungoogled-chromium</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/ungoogled/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/ungoogled/</guid><description>As one of the most used applications in the system, it is ideal to have a secure browser. Browsers have large attack surface due to a combination of their complexity, handling of untrusted input, and use of unsafe languages. Even while browser makers continually work make their browsers more secure, most browsers have poor privacy out of the box. ungoogled-chromium is an often recommended browser because of its approach of stripping out Google web services from Chromium.</description></item></channel></rss>