<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>segmentation fault</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on segmentation fault</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://qua3k.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>New Year, New Blog</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/new-year-new-blog/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/new-year-new-blog/</guid><description>It is a new year, and that means a new blog theme. I honestly think this looks great.
hik if you kang this one more again</description></item><item><title>Improving Browser Security</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/hexavalent/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/hexavalent/</guid><description>Hexavalent is a security and privacy focused web browser based on the open source Chromium project. It seeks to develop meaningful security improvements focusing on mitigating classes of bugs rather than individual vulnerabilities and is currently an unfinished product.</description></item><item><title>Standard Streams</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/stdout/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/stdout/</guid><description>Today I learned about standard streams. I now have a deeper understanding of computers than ever before.</description></item><item><title>Some Thoughts About the NSO Group's Pegasus</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/pegasus/</link><pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/pegasus/</guid><description>Recently, a story has been making the rounds about the ‘new’ Pegasus spyware that has lead to mass panic in technical circles that has users worried. There are some questions that users might ask that haven’t been accurately answered and the events have been used by various companies to market their product.</description></item><item><title>Hacking Whonix onto Hyper-V</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/guides/whonix/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/guides/whonix/</guid><description>This guide aims to get the Whonix™ operating system running on Hyper-V. This guide does not expect Virtualbox specific features such as guest additions to work and does not expend any effort to make them work.</description></item><item><title>Email (In)security</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/security/email/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/security/email/</guid><description>There is no such thing as secure email. Email is an inherently insecure protocol, conceived at a time when security was an afterthought. There are fundamental flaws with email that cannot be mitigated by slapping encryption on top.</description></item><item><title>ungoogled-chromium</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/ungoogled/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/ungoogled/</guid><description>The ungoogled-chromium project is an often recommended browser to people seeking a private Chromium-based browser. However, many people are unaware that their patches often regress the privacy/security rather than improve it.
Toolchain Hardening ungoogled-chromium produces some automatic builds through GitHub Actions, as well as delegating third parties to produce &amp;ldquo;contributor binaries&amp;rdquo;. Disregarding the problems with entrusting third parties for builds, all of the builds weaken the security of the existing mitigations in some form.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/about/</guid><description>About me</description></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/first/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/first/</guid><description>hi
i am cool</description></item></channel></rss>