<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>duck's pond</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on duck's pond</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://qua3k.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/about/</guid><description>Hi there 👋
im a duck
i use arch btw
aidan is jealous of my chad hugo site</description></item><item><title>Hacking Whonix onto Hyper-V</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/guides/whonix/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/guides/whonix/</guid><description>Introduction Prerequisites Installation Extraction Conversion Networking Create the internal switch Create the gateway Configure the network Create the private switch VM creation Gateway Workstation Hyper-V networking Generation 2 installation Converting to vhdx Install grub-efi Partitioning Mount partitions Load the efivars kernel module Finish the GRUB install Unmount and reboot Problems Introduction This guide aims to get the Whonix™ operating system running on Hyper-V.</description></item><item><title>Email (In)security</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/security/email/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/security/email/</guid><description>There is no such thing as secure email. Email is an inherently insecure protocol, conceived at a time when security was an afterthought. There are fundamental flaws with email that cannot be mitigated by slapping encryption on top.
Problems with… Email Authentication Sender Policy Framework is a protocol used to authorize the mail transfer agents allowed to send mail on behalf of a domain. However, SPF alone is almost useless in protecting against spoofing as it is designed to protect against forged senders and not forged headers shown in clients.</description></item><item><title>ungoogled-chromium</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/ungoogled/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/ungoogled/</guid><description>As one of the most used applications in the system, it is ideal to have a secure browser. Browsers have large attack surface due to a combination of their complexity, handling of untrusted input, and use of unsafe languages. Even while browser makers continually work make their browsers more secure, most browsers have poor privacy out of the box. ungoogled-chromium is an often recommended browser because of its approach of stripping out Google web services from Chromium.</description></item><item><title>First Post</title><link>https://qua3k.github.io/first/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://qua3k.github.io/first/</guid><description>hi
i am cool</description></item></channel></rss>